A Guide to the Laurance S. Rockefeller papers, Office and Home Files FA1353
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Personal Papers and Interests, 1888-2010; 1; 118.83 Cubic Feet 281 containers.
  - Mary French Rockefeller and Family Files, 1888-2008; 1_2
    - MFR-LSR - Christmas/Holiday Cards - Received, 1955-1957 (Box 243, Folder 1)
    - MFR - Christmas/Holiday Cards - Received, 1956 (Box 201, Folder 1)
    - MFR - Christmas/Holiday Cards - Received, 1958 (Box 201, Folder 2)
    - MFR - Christmas/Holiday Cards - Received, 1959 (Box 201, Folder 3)
    - MFR - Christmas/Holiday Cards, 1959 (Box 339, Folder 2)
    - LSR-MFR - Christmas/Holiday Cards, 1960s (Box 187, Folder 3)
    - MFR-LSR - Christmas/Holiday Cards - Received, 1961 (Box 242, Folder 3)
    - MFR-LSR - Christmas/Holiday Cards - Received, 1962 (Box 243, Folder 2)
    - MFR-LSR - Christmas/Holiday Cards - Received, 1963 (Box 243, Folder 3)
    - MFR-LSR - Christmas/Holiday Cards - Received, 1965 (Box 243, Folder 4)
    - MFR-LSR - Christmas/Holiday Cards - Received, 1966 (Box 243, Folder 5)
    - MFR-LSR - Christmas/Holiday Cards - Received, 1967 (Box 244, Folder 1)
    - MFR-LSR - Christmas/Holiday Cards - Received, 1969 (Box 243, Folder 6)
    - MFR-LSR - Christmas/Holiday Cards - Received, 1970-1971 (Box 244, Folder 2)
    - MFR-LSR - Christmas/Holiday Cards - Received, 1972 (Box 244, Folder 3)
    - MFR-LSR - Christmas/Holiday Cards - Received, 1977-1980 (Box 244, Folder 4, Box 245, Folder 1)
    - LSR-MFR - Christmas/Holiday Cards, 1970-1985 (Box 181, Folder 5-6)
    - LSR-MFR - Christmas/Holiday Cards, 1986-1996 (Box 182, Folder 1-3)
    - LSR-MFR - Christmas/Holiday Cards, 1980s (Box 187, Folder 4)
    - LSR-MFR - Christmas/Holiday Cards, undated (Box 187, Folder 5)
    - MFR - Christmas/Holiday Cards - Received, 1990s (Box 201, Folder 4-6, Box 202, Folder 1-4, Box 203)
    - MFR-LSR - Christmas/Holiday Cards - Received, 1980s-1990s (Box 331, Folder 1-3, Box 332, Folder 1-4, Box 333, Folder 1)
    - LSR - Christmas, 1997 (Box 245, Folder 2)
    - LSR - Christmas/Holiday Cards - Received, 1997 (Box 245, Folder 3-5, Box 246, Folder 1-4, Box 247, Box 248, Folder 1-3)
    - LSR - Christmas, 1989-1997 (Box 248, Folder 4)
    - LSR - Christmas and Birthday, 1998 (Box 248, Folder 5)
    - LSR - Christmas, 1998 (Box 249, Folder 1)
    - LSR - Christmas, 1999 (Box 249, Folder 2-3)
    - LSR - Christmas, 2000 (Box 249, Folder 4, Box 250, Folder 1)
    - LSR - Christmas, 2001 (Box 250, Folder 2-4, Box 251, Folder 1)
    - MFR-LSR - Christmas/Holiday Cards - Cartier Cards - To Send, undated (Box 307, Folder 3)
    - MFR-LSR - Christmas Luncheon, Playhouse - Cartier Invitations - To Send, 1995 (Box 307, Folder 4)
    - MFR-LSR - Christmas/Holiday Cards - Cartier Cards - To Send, 1982-1984; 1994 (Box 307, Folder 5)
    - MFR-LSR - Christmas/Holiday Cards - Cartier Cards - To Send, 1965 (Box 307, Folder 6)
    - MFR-LSR - Christmas/Holiday Cards - Cartier Cards - To Send, 1968 (Box 307, Folder 7)
    - MFR-LSR - Christmas/Holiday Cards - Cartier Cards - To Send, 1987 (Box 307, Folder 8)
    - MFR-LSR - Christmas/Holiday Cards - Cartier Cards - To Send, 1989 (Box 307, Folder 9)
    - LSR - Family Matters - Miscellaneous, 1997-2003 (Box 185, Folder 1)
    - MFR - Personal Letters and Papers, 1950s-1960s (Box 189, Folder 5, Box 190, Folder 1-3, Box 191)
    - MFR - Personal Letters and Papers, 1990s (Box 193, Folder 3)
    - MFR - Family and Friends - Letters and Cards (Box 196, Folder 1-2)
    - MFR - LSR and Family - Correspondence, Letters and Photos (Box 196, Folder 3, Box 197, Folder 1-2)
    - LSR - Scrapbook and Clippings, 1930s-1980s (Box 197, Folder 3-4, Box 193, Folder 4)
    - LSR - Scrapbook - Remarks and Events, 1948-1991 (Box 338, Folder 4-5)
    - MFR - Cuttings for Scrapbooks, 1948-1950 (Box 278, Folder 1)
    - MFR - Cuttings for Scrapbooks, 1956 (Box 278, Folder 2)
    - MFR - Cuttings for Scrapbooks, 1957 (Box 278, Folder 3-4)
    - MFR - Cuttings for Scrapbooks, 1958 (Box 278, Folder 5)
    - MFR - Cuttings for Scrapbooks, 1959-1962 (Box 278, Folder 6)
    - MFR - Cuttings for Scrapbooks, 1962-1964 (Box 279, Folder 1)
    - MFR - Cuttings for Scrapbooks, 1964-1965 (Box 279, Folder 2-3)
    - MFR - Cuttings for Scrapbooks, 1965-1966 (Box 279, Folder 4)
    - MFR - Cuttings for Scrapbooks, 1967 (Box 279, Folder 5)
    - MFR - Cuttings for Scrapbooks, 1968 (Box 280, Folder 1)
    - MFR-LSR - Personal Letters - Laura and Family (Box 194, Folder 1-2)
    - MFR-LSR - Personal Letters - Laura and Richard and Family (Box 209, Folder 2-3)
    - MFR-LSR - Personal Letters - Marion and Family (Box 194, Folder 3-4, Box 195, Folder 1)
    - MFR-LSR - Personal Letters - Marion and Family - Rachel and Alejandro Ortiz (Box 209, Folder 1)
    - MFR-LSR - Personal Letters - Lucy and Family (Box 195, Folder 2-4)
    - MFR-LSR - Personal Letters - Larry and Family (Box 195, Folder 5-6, Box 186, Folder 13-14)
    - MFR-LSR - Rockefeller Family Correspondence, 1940s-1980s (Box 198, Folder 1)
    - MFR-LSR - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1970s-1990s (Box 198, Folder 4)
    - MFR-LSR - Correspondence - Rutherford (Box 199, Folder 1)
    - MFR-LSR - Correspondence - President Lyndon and Ladybird Johnson, 1960s-1990s (Box 199, Folder 2)
    - MFR-LSR - Correspondence - President George H.W. and Barbara Bush, 1990s (Box 199, Folder 3)
    - LSR-MFR - 834 Fifth Avenue, 1987-1988 (Box 193, Folder 5)
      Alterations, yearly upkeep.
    - LSR - Birthday, 2002 May 26 (Box 207, Folder 1)
    - LSR - 93rd Birthday, 2003 May 26 (Box 207, Folder 2)
    - Memorial Sloan Kettering, 1981-1989 (Box 207, Folder 3)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1930s-1974 (Box 207, Folder 5)
    - Princeton University, 1950-1951 (Box 207, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller Center, 1962 (Box 207, Folder 7)
    - LSR Speeches, 1960-1984 (Box 208, Folder 1)
    - Woodstock, 1981-1993 (Box 208, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Events, 1970s-1990s (Box 208, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous Articles, 1940s-2005 (Box 208, Folder 4)
    - Family Christmas Lunch, 2004 (Box 208, Folder 5)
    - LSR - Thanksgiving, 1997-2003 (Box 208, Folder 6)
    - LSR - Wolfe, Jane Lee (JJ), 1992-2004 (Box 208, Folder 7)
    - LSR - Zorach - "Devotion" Sculture - Removal, 2004-2005 (Box 209, Folder 4)
    - MFR - Watercolor Painting, 1963-1973 (Box 210, Folder 1)
    - MSKCC - A Tribute to LSR Book, 1997 December 16 (Box 210, Folder 2)
      Presented to LSR, 1997 December 16.
    - JY Ranch and Valley Ranch - Sotheby's Appraisal, 1989 June 28 (Box 210, Folder 3)
    - LSR - Estate of JDR Jr. - Articles Bequest, 1971 (Box 210, Folder 4)
    - LSR - David Rockefeller - "Goodbye" Call, 2004 July 12 (Box 210, Folder 5)
    - LSR - Letter to President George W. Bush, 1990 May 30 (Box 210, Folder 6)
    - LSR - Family Christmas Luncheon - LSR Host, 2002 (Box 210, Folder 7)
    - MFR - 834 Fifth Avenue papers - Letters, Clippings and Activities, 1930s-1940s (Box 210, Folder 8, Box 213, Folder 4)
    - MFR - 834 Fifth Avenue papers - School/College Notes and Yearbook, 1920s (Box 211, Folder 4, Box 213, Folder 1-3)
    - MFR - 834 Fifth Avenue papers - Museum of Modern Art (MoMA), 1930s (Box 211, Folder 1)
    - MFR - 834 Fifth Avenue papers - MFR-LSR Engagement/Wedding Correspondence, 1930s (Box 211, Folder 2-3)
    - MFR - 834 Fifth Avenue papers - MFR-LSR Wedding - Letters and Clippings, 1934 (Box 212, Folder 1-2)
    - MFR - 834 Fifth Avenue papers - MFR-LSR Wedding - Guest List, 1934 (Box 212, Folder 3)
    - MFR - 834 Fifth Avenue papers - Elizabeth French-Ethan Hitchcock Wedding - Clippings, 1937 (Box 212, Folder 4)
    - MFR - 834 Fifth Avenue papers - Paris Addresses, 1930s (Box 212, Folder 5)
    - MFR - 834 Fifth Avenue papers - Christmas Cards, 1930s (Box 212, Folder 6)
    - MFR-LSR - Christmas/Holiday Cards - Received, 1950s (Box 214, Folder 1)
    - MFR-LSR - Christmas/Holiday Cards - Received, 1990s (Box 219, Folder 2)
    - MFR - 834 Fifth Avenue - Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1945-1946 (Box 268, Folder 5)
    - MFR - 834 Fifth Avenue - Belgian Congo, 1940s (Box 268, Folder 6)
    - MFR - 834 Fifth Avenue - Philanthropic Interests, 1940s-1950s (Box 269, Folder 1-2)
    - MFR - 834 Fifth Avenue - Society of Memorial Cancer Center, 1950s (Box 269, Folder 3)
    - MFR - 834 Fifth Avenue - South Africa, 1962 (Box 269, Folder 4)
    - MFR - 834 Fifth Avenue - Membership Cards (Box 269, Folder 5)
    - MFR - 834 Fifth Avenue - JDR 150th Anniversary Celebration, 1989 October 26-28 (Box 269, Folder 6)
    - MFR - 834 Fifth Avenue - Early YWCA papers, 1920s (Box 269, Folder 7, Box 270, Folder 1)
    - MFR - YWCA Correspondence, 1955 (Box 214, Folder 2-4)
    - MFR - YWCA, 1940s-1960s (Box 276, Folder 5)
    - MFR - Miscellaneous Letters (Box 276, Folder 6)
    - MFR - 834 Fifth Avenue - Accident - Letters Received, 1970 June (Box 270, Folder 2-3, Box 271, Folder 1)
    - MFR - 834 Fifth Avenue - General Files, 1940s-1980s (Box 271, Folder 2-4, Box 272, Folder 1-3)
    - MFR - Elizabeth French Hitchcock Sympathy Letters, 1976-1977 (Box 215, Folder 1)
    - MFR - Marion R. Weber Wedding, 1965 (Box 218, Folder 1)
    - MFR - Lucy R. Waletzky Wedding, 1964 and 1970 (Box 218, Folder 2-3)
    - MFR - Miscellaneous Correspondence and Cards, 1940s (Box 216, Folder 1-3)
    - MFR - Miscellaneous Correspondence and Cards, 1960s-1980s (Box 216, Folder 4, Box 217, Folder 1-4)
    - MFR - Miscellaneous Correspondence and Cards, 1960s-1990s (Box 215, Folder 2-3)
    - MFR - Letters from Family - French (Box 221, Folder 2-3)
    - MFR - Letters from Family - John French - Sympathy, 1984 (Box 221, Folder 4)
    - MFR - Letters from Friends, 1930s-1970s (Box 220, Folder 2-4, Box 221, Folder 1)
    - MFR - Letters from Friends, 1978-1989 (Box 218, Folder 4-5, Box 219, Folder 1)
    - MFR - Letters from Friends, 1970s-1990s (Box 222, Folder 3-4, Box 223, Folder 1-4)
    - MFR - Central Park Zoo - Birthday Tribute, 2003 (Box 219, Folder 3)
    - MFR - Events, Programs and Catalogs, 1965-1980s (Box 219, Folder 4-5, Box 220, Folder 1)
    - MFR - Activities - Letters, 1951-1970s (Box 222, Folder 1)
    - MFR - Family - Articles, 1920s-1980s (Box 222, Folder 2)
    - MFR - Sympathy and Condolences Received, 1970s (Box 224, Folder 1-3, Box 225, Folder 1-2)
    - MFR-LSR - 50th Wedding Anniversary - JY Ranch, 1984 August 15 (Box 225, Folder 3)
    - MFR-LSR - 50th Wedding Anniversary - Letters and Cards, 1984 (Box 225, Folder 4, Box 226, Folder 1)
    - MFR-LSR - 50th Wedding Anniversary, 1984 (Box 302, Folder 5)
    - MFR-LSR - 60th Wedding Anniversary - Logistics, 1994 (Box 302, Folder 6)
    - MFR-LSR - 60th Wedding Anniversary - Attendees, 1994 (Box 302, Folder 7)
    - MFR-LSR - 60th Wedding Anniversary - Accommodations, Gifts, Declinations, 1994 (Box 303, Folder 1)
    - MFR-LSR - 60th Wedding Anniversary - Dinner, 1994 (Box 303, Folder 2)
    - MFR-LSR - 60th Wedding Anniversary - Well Wishes, 1994 (Box 303, Folder 3)
    - MFR-LSR - Passports, 1931; 1962-1996 (Box 226, Folder 3)
    - MFR - Sheet Music, 1921-1950s (Box 252, Folder 1)
    - MFR-LSR - Woodstock - Billings Farm and Museum Album, 1996 (Box 252, Folder 2)
    - MFR - Woodstock - Marsh Billings Historical Park, 1992 (Box 280, Folder 6)
    - MFR - School Notes and Papers, 1930s (Box 280, Folder 2-3)
    - MFR - The Blue Hill Troupe, 1940s (Box 280, Folder 4)
    - MFR - The Asia Foundation, 1958 (Box 280, Folder 5)
    - MFR - Union Church of Pocantico Hills, 1983-1990 (Box 280, Folder 7)
    - MFR - School Pamphlets, 1920s (Box 281, Folder 1)
    - MFR - Pamphlets - Photography, 1920s (Box 281, Folder 2-3)
    - MFR - General MacArthur's Credo (Box 281, Folder 4)
    - MFR - Mary M. Billings French (Mother) - Collected Quotations, 1920s (Box 290, Folder 3)
    - MFR - Mary M. Billings French (Mother) - Collected Quotations, 1930s (Box 291, Folder 1-2)
    - MFR - Mary M. Billings French (Mother) - Collected Quotations, 1940s (Box 291, Folder 3)
    - MFR - Mary M. Billings French (Mother) - Collected Quotations, 1920s (Box 411, Folder 2-3)
    - MFR - Mary M. Billings French (Mother) - Collected Quotations, 1930 (Box 411, Folder 4)
    - MFR - Mary M. Billings French (Mother) - Collected Quotations, 1937 (Box 411, Folder 5)
    - MFR - Mary M. Billings French (Mother) - Collected Quotations, 1939-1940 (Box 412, Folder 1-3)
    - MFR - Mary M. Billings French (Mother) - Collected Quotations, 1943 (Box 412, Folder 4)
    - MFR - Letters to Mary French Rockefeller, 1925-1926 (Box 326, Folder 4)
    - MFR - Letters to Mary French Rockefeller, 1927 (Box 327, Folder 1-3)
    - MFR - Letters to Mary French Rockefeller, 1928 (Box 327, Folder 4)
    - MFR - Letters to Mary French Rockefeller, 1929 (Box 328, Folder 1-2)
    - MFR - Letters to Mary French Rockefeller, 1930 (Box 328, Folder 3)
    - MFR - Letters to Mary French Rockefeller, 1931-1932 (Box 328, Folder 4)
    - MFR - Letters to Mary French Rockefeller, 1933 (Box 329, Folder 1)
    - MFR - Letters to Mary French Rockefeller, 1934 (Box 329, Folder 2)
    - MFR - Letters of Sympathy, 1935 (Box 377, Folder 1)
    - LSR Family - Miscellaneous Photographs - Family and Friends (Box 335, Folder 1-4)
    - Religion - Crestone Mountain, Zen Center, 1991-1997 (Box 336, Folder 6-7)
    - MFR - Awards - Miscellaneous (Box 338, Folder 1)
    - MFR - United Board of Christian Higher Education in Asia - Meeting, 1992 November 16 (Box 338, Folder 2)
    - LSR - Leatherbound Edition of Le Grand Meaulnes, Alain Fournier, 1925-1926 (Box 339, Folder 5)
      Inscribed to LSR by the author, 1926.
    - LSR - Pocantico Hills Maps - JDR Jr. to Children, 1956 (Box 341, Folder 1)
    - MFR-LSR - Guest Book, 1941-1996 (Box 340, Folder 1)
    - MFR-LSR - Book of Wedding Gifts, 1934 August 15 (Box 340, Folder 2)
    - MFR-LSR - Yachting Guest Book, 1950-1977 (Box 340, Folder 3)
    - MFR - Dinner Guest Book, 1946-1980s (Box 340, Folder 4)
    - MFR - Music Therapy Class - Book of Songs, 1996 (Box 342, Folder 1)
    - LSR - Framed, illuminated Prayer of St. Francis (Box 342, Folder 3)
      with "Mr. R. office" handwritten on back
    - MFR-LSR - 50th Wedding Anniversary - Memorabilia and Guest Book, 1984 (Box 342, Folder 4)
    - MFR-LSR - Wedding - Newspaper Clippings, 1934 (Box 343, Folder 2-5, Box 344, Folder 1-3)
    - MFR - Foreign Policy Association - Headline Series Pamphlets, 1971-1985 (Box 344, Folder 4)
    - MFR - Executive Ministries, 1991-1992 (Box 344, Folder 5)
    - MFR - Gordon-Conwell Theological Seminary, 1994-1997 (Box 344, Folder 6)
    - MFR - General Correspondence and Clippings, 1988-1997 (Box 344, Folder 7)
    - MFR - United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia - Meeting, 1996 November (Box 345, Folder 1)
    - MFR - YWCA - National Convention, 1988 June (Box 345, Folder 2)
    - MFR - YWCA Files, 1950s (Box 345, Folder 3-5)
    - MFR - YWCA - National Convention, 1961 May 8-13 (Box 346, Folder 1)
    - MFR - YWCA - National Board - Centennial, 1950s (Box 346, Folder 2-4, Box 347, Folder 1)
    - MFR - YWCA Files, 1969-1980 (Box 347, Folder 2-3)
    - MFR - YWCA - Centennial - Reports, 1955 (Box 407, Folder 1-2)
    - MFR - YWCA - Centennial - Printed Material, 1955 (Box 407, Folder 3-4)
    - MFR - St. Faith's House, 1948-1973 (Box 347, Folder 4)
    - MFR - St. Faith's House - Building Fund, 1950-1952 (Box 347, Folder 5)
    - LSR - Lucy Rockefeller Waletzky, 1962-2003 (Box 348, Folder 1)
    - MFR - Memorial Service - Guest Lists, 1997 (Box 348, Folder 2)
    - MFR - YWCA Files, 1950s (Box 349, Folder 1)
    - MFR - YWCA Files, 1960s (Box 349, Folder 2)
    - MFR - YWCA - Travel Files - Mexico, 1959 (Box 349, Folder 3)
    - MFR - YWCA - Travel Files - China, 1985 (Box 349, Folder 4)
    - MFR - YWCA - Travel Files - Japan, 1980 (Box 349, Folder 5, Box 350, Folder 1)
    - MFR - YWCA - Travel Files, 1960s (Box 350, Folder 2-3)
    - MFR - YWCA - Travel Files - India, 1960s (Box 350, Folder 4-5)
    - MFR - YWCA - Travel Files - Africa, 1960s (Box 350, Folder 6)
    - MFR - YWCA - Travel Files, 1960s-1970s (Box 351, Folder 1-3)
    - MFR - YWCA - World Council Meeting, 1971 August (Box 351, Folder 4)
    - MFR - YWCA - Travel Files - Travel Files - National Geographic Trip, Korea, 1963 (Box 352, Folder 1-2)
    - MFR - YWCA - Travel Files - Jerusalem, 1961 (Box 352, Folder 3)
    - MFR - YWCA - Travel Files - South Pacific, 1970s (Box 352, Folder 4)
    - MFR - YWCA - Travel Files - South America, 1960s (Box 352, Folder 5)
    - MFR - YWCA - Travel Files - Hong Kong, 1961-1962 (Box 352, Folder 6)
    - MFR - YWCA - Travel Files - National Geographic, 1962-1966 (Box 352, Folder 7-8)
    - MFR - YWCA - Travel Files, 1960s-1980s (Box 353, Folder 1-3)
    - MFR - YWCA - Travel Files - Philippines, 1962-1963 (Box 353, Folder 4)
    - MFR - YWCA - Travel Files - Australia, 1960s-1970s (Box 353, Folder 5)
    - MFR - Smithsonian - Travel Files - Greece, 1979 (Box 354, Folder 1)
    - MFR - Meetings - Travel Files - San Antonio Missions National Historic Park, 1980 (Box 354, Folder 2)
    - MFR - Meetings - Travel Files - Eastern Airlines Board of Directors, Argentina (Box 354, Folder 3)
    - MFR - Meetings - National Committee on US-China Relations, China, 1985 October (Box 354, Folder 4)
    - MFR - Meetings - Travel Files, 1963 (Box 354, Folder 5)
    - MFR - YWCA - Travel Files - Buenos Aires, 1962-1963 (Box 354, Folder 6)
    - MFR - Meetings - Princeton Art Museum, 1979-1980 (Box 354, Folder 7)
    - MFR - Meetings - Spelman College, 1950s-1980 (Box 355, Folder 1-3)
    - MFR - Spelman College - Publications, 1950s-1970s (Box 356, Folder 1)
    - MFR - Spelman College - General, 1940s-1960s (Box 356, Folder 2-3)
    - MFR - Travel Files - France and England, 1980 (Box 356, Folder 4)
    - MFR - Rockefeller University - Report on a Visit to China (PRC), 1977 May (Box 356, Folder 5)
    - MFR - Spelman College - Development Fund, 1960s (Box 357, Folder 1)
    - MFR - Spelman College - Capital Funds, 1950s (Box 357, Folder 2)
    - MFR - St. Faith's House Foundation, 1973-1974 (Box 357, Folder 3)
    - MFR - YWCA - International Training Institute, 1965 (Box 357, Folder 4)
    - MFR - White House Conference on International Cooperation, 1965 (Box 357, Folder 5)
    - MFR - YWCA - National Board Correspondence, 1950s (Box 357, Folder 6)
    - MFR - YWCA - International Training Institute, 1965 (Box 358, Folder 1)
    - MFR - YWCA - World Council Meetings, 1963-1967 (Box 358, Folder 2-3)
    - MFR - National Council of Churches, 1963-1965 (Box 358, Folder 4)
    - MFR - YWCA - National Board - Convention Committee, 1950s (Box 358, Folder 5)
    - MFR - International Conference of Social Work, 1966 (Box 358, Folder 6)
    - MFR - UN Study Group, 1962-1969 (Box 359, Folder 1)
    - MFR - Travel Files - Union Pacific Trip, 1969 (Box 359, Folder 2)
    - MFR - Colony Club - Arts and Literature Committee, 1951-1958 (Box 359, Folder 3)
    - MFR - Family - Marion's Debut, 1956 December 20 (Box 359, Folder 4)
    - MFR - Family - Laura's Debut, 1959 December 19 (Box 359, Folder 5)
    - MFR - Girl Scout Council, 1957-1968 (Box 359, Folder 6)
    - MFR - YWCA - World Service Council, 1996 April (Box 359, Folder 7)
    - MFR - New York Community Trust, Meeting, 1997 February 6 (Box 359, Folder 8)
    - MFR - YWCA - Dillon, Douglas, 1958-1989 (Box 359, Folder 9)
    - MFR - YWCA - Astor Foundation, 1966 (Box 359, Folder 10)
    - MFR - YWCA - American Express, 1962-1976 (Box 359, Folder 11)
    - MFR - YWCA - Allied Chemical Corporation, 1971-1986 (Box 360, Folder 1)
    - MFR - YWCA - Exxon Corporation, 1967-1989 (Box 360, Folder 2)
    - MFR - Get Well Cards - Surgery, 1986 June (Box 360, Folder 3-4)
    - MFR - Weekly Appointments Calendar, 1996 (Box 360, Folder 5)
    - LSR - Personal, 1986-2004 (Box 360, Folder 6)
    - LSR - A Christian Ministry in the National Parks - Annual Meeting, 1997 September (Box 360, Folder 7)
    - MFR - Cards and Well Wishes, 1997 (Box 360, Folder 8)
    - MFR - 1910-1997 - Tribute Scrapbook (Box 361, Folder 1)
    - MFR - YWCA - Scrapbook, 1952-1955 (Box 361, Folder 2)
    - MFR - Memorial Service - Brick Presbyterian Church, NYC, 1997 May 14 (Box 361, Folder 3)
    - JDR Jr - Tribute - Kiefau - A Gift from Queen Salote Tubou, Tonga, 1927 (Box 362)
      with letter from George Vincent, 1927.
    - MFR - President George H. W. Bush Correspondence, 1990-1993 (Box 363, Folder 5)
    - MFR - Trip to Russia - Foreign Policy Association, 1989 (Box 364, Folder 1)
    - MFR - Foreign Policy Association, 1989 (Box 364, Folder 2)
    - MFR - Trip to China - Foreign Policy Association, 1985 (Box 364, Folder 3)
    - LSR - Rachel Weber Wedding, 1990 August 18 (Box 364, Folder 4)
    - MFR - Tasmanian Youth Theatre, 1968 (Box 364, Folder 5)
    - LSR - JY Ranch Photographs, 2001 (Box 364, Folder 6)
    - LSR - Photographs - Kent House, Pocantico (Box 364, Folder 7)
    - LSR - Postcards (Box 365, Folder 1)
    - LSR - Photographs - Hawaii (Box 365, Folder 2)
    - LSR - Photographs - Maine (Box 365, Folder 3)
    - LSR - Photographs - Caribbean (Box 365, Folder 4)
    - LSR - Photographs and Negatives - Miscellaneous (Box 365, Folder 5-6)
    - LSR - Valentine's Day, 2003 (Box 366, Folder 1)
    - LSR - Birthday Wishes, 2000 (Box 366, Folder 2)
    - LSR - Birthday Wishes, 1990-1995 (Box 366, Folder 3)
    - LSR - Birthdays and Greetings - Miscellaneous (Box 366, Folder 4)
    - MFR - Action Folder, 1997 (Box 367, Folder 7)
    - MFR - YWCA - International Building Fund, 1994-1995 (Box 367, Folder 8)
    - MFR - YWCA Files, 1997 (Box 367, Folder 9)
    - LSR - Correspondence, 1980s-1990s (Box 367, Folder 11)
    - MFR - MSKCC - Memorial Art Committee, 1980s-1997 (Box 368, Folder 1)
    - MFR - Prayer Book, 1920s (Box 368, Folder 2)
    - MFR - Metropolitan Museum of Art - Chinese Poetry Seminar, 1985 (Box 368, Folder 3-4)
    - MFR - Thank You Letters - Christmas, Fractured Hip, 1996 (Box 368, Folder 5)
    - MFR - Pocantico Hills - Gardening, Greenhouse, 1950s (Box 368, Folder 6)
    - MFR - MSKCC - Memorial Art Committee, 1973-1982 (Box 369, Folder 1-2)
    - MFR - Events, 1950s-1990s (Box 369, Folder 3-4)
    - MFR-LSR - Events, 1950s-1970s (Box 370, Folder 1-2)
    - MFR - YWCA, 1960s-1988 (Box 370, Folder 3)
    - MFR - Trip - Santa Fe, 1957 Summer (Box 370, Folder 4)
    - MFR - Trip - Europe, 1952 (Box 370, Folder 5)
    - LSR - Princeton, 1932 (Box 371, Folder 1)
    - LSR - Conservation (Box 371, Folder 2)
    - LSR - Notes (including Harvard Law) (Box 371, Folder 3-4)
    - LSR - Dartmouth - NAR Center (Box 371, Folder 5)
    - LSR - LSR Family, 1944 (Box 371, Folder 6)
    - LSR - Letters from Family and Friends, 1930-2004 (Box 371, Folder 7)
    - LSR - Diary, 1926 (Box 371, Folder 8-9)
    - LSR-MFR - Inventories and Appraisals of Tangible Personal Property of Lucy Truman Aldrich, 1955 (Box 372, Folder 1)
    - LSR - LSR Family - Miscellaneous Photos (Box 372, Folder 2)
    - LSR - Personal - Baptismal Certificate (Box 372, Folder 3)
    - LSR - Personal - Early Lessons, 1913-1914; 1923 (Box 372, Folder 4)
    - LSR - Personal - Lock of Hair from Laura Spelman Rockefeller (Box 372, Folder 5)
      Given to Laurance S. Rockefeller by JDR Jr.
    - MFR - Christmas Presents, 1936-1996 (Box 373, Folder 1)
    - MFR - Weekly Planners, 1986-1987; 1990 (Box 373, Folder 2)
    - MFR - Weekly Planners, 1991-1992; 1994-1995; 1997 (Box 373, Folder 3)
    - MFR - Diary, 1924 (Box 373, Folder 4)
    - MFR - Wedding Expense Account, 1934 (Box 373, Folder 5)
    - MFR - New York Community Trust - Publications, 1986-1990 (Box 373, Folder 6)
    - MFR - YWCA - City of New York, 1984-1995 (Box 374, Folder 1)
    - MFR - Foundation for Child Development - Publications, 1990 (Box 374, Folder 2)
    - MFR - Foreign Policy Association - Publications - Headline Series, 1970s-1990 (Box 374, Folder 3-4)